all_questions = {
    "questions": [{
        "question": "A computer program that translates one statement of program instructions at a time into machine language is called",
        "correct_answer": "Compiler",
        "options": [
          "CPU",
          "Interpreter",
          "Compiler",
          "Simulator"
        ]
      },
  
      {
        "question": " NTFS stands for?",
        "correct_answer": "New Technology File System ",
        "options": ["New Trend File Saving",
          "Network File Saving",
          "New Technology File System ",
          "None Of These"
        ]
      },
  
      {
        "question": "Which variable type can have only two possible values?",
        "correct_answer": "bool",
        "options": ["Integer",
          "String",
          "double",
          "bool"
        ],
  
      },
  
      {
        "question": " In computer science and information technology (IT), DNS is an abbreviation of",
        "options": ["Direct Name System",
          "Domain Name System",
          "Direct Name Software",
          "Domain Name Software"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Domain Name System"
      },
      {
        "question": "In C++, the library function exit() causes an exit from the",
        "options": ["statement",
          "loop in which it occurs",
          "function in which it occurs",
          "program in which it occurs"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "program in which it occurs"
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In C++, a function name must be followed by",
        "correct_answer": "parentheses",
        "options": [
          "braces",
          "parentheses",
          "statement",
          "variable name"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which of these is a high-level machine-oriented language for the machines that are of the GEC 4080 series?",
        "correct_answer": "Babbage",
        "options": [
          "ALGOL",
          "Babbage",
          "SNOBOL",
          " LOGO"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which of these refers to a systems programming language for the Intel family microcomputers?",
        "correct_answer": "PL/M",
        "options": [
          "PLA",
          "PL/CT",
          "PL/M",
          "PL/C"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": " What is the CPU\’s section that interprets, selects, and also sees to a program instructions\’ execution?",
        "correct_answer": "Control unit",
        "options": [
          "Register unit",
          "Control unit",
          "ALU",
          "Memory"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": " What access method do we use to obtain any record out of a cassette tape?",
        "correct_answer": "Sequential",
        "options": [
          "Random",
          " Direct",
          "Sequential",
          "All of the above"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The 1\’s complement of 10 is:",
        "correct_answer": "01",
        "options": [
          "10",
          "11",
          "110",
          "01"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the common boundary present between two systems known as?",
        "correct_answer": "Interface",
        "options": [
          "Interface",
          "Surface",
          "Interdiction",
          "None of the above"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": " _____________ is a computer that has been designed so that it is as compact as possible.",
        "correct_answer": "Microcomputer",
        "options": [
          "Supercomputer",
          "Mini",
          "Mainframe",
          "Microcomputer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which command is used to display the top of the file?",
        "correct_answer": "head",
        "options": [
          "cat",
          "head",
          "more",
          "grep"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Out of the following, which one is still useful if we want to add numbers?",
        "correct_answer": "Abacus",
        "options": [
          "UNIVAC",
          "Abacus",
          "ENIAC",
          "EDSAC"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the number used to control the forms of other numbers known as?",
        "correct_answer": "Mask",
        "options": [
          "Mask",
          "Map",
          "Marker",
          "Mantissa"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "One packet on any data link is called:",
        "correct_answer": "Frame",
        "options": [
          "Group",
          " Block",
          "Frame",
          "Path"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "A total of how many bit codes are used for TELEPRINTER machines by Murray code?",
        "correct_answer": "5",
        "options": [
          "25",
          "9",
          "5",
          "4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": " A list of various coded instructions is known as:",
        "correct_answer": "Computer program",
        "options": [
          "Flowchart",
          "Utility programs",
          "Algorithm",
          "Computer program"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which command is used to sort the lines of data in a file in reverse order in UNIX?",
        "correct_answer": "sort -r",
        "options": [
          "sort",
          "sh",
          "st",
          "sort -r"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
  
 